We are experiencing intermittent issues with our INFO24 system.  We are working to resolve the issue. We apologize for any inconvenience. [Online](https://ebanking.communityfirstfl.org/cfcufonline/Uux.aspx?&_ga=2.251178950.1341183297.1604520138-1814686001.1604520138#/login "Click here to go to the Online Banking login page") and [Mobile Banking](https://www.communityfirstfl.org/personal-banking/online-banking "Learn more about Mobile Banking") are available during this time.

All branches and headquarters will be closed in observance of Columbus Day/Indigenous People's Day,  **Monday, Oct. 14.**  [Info24](https://www.communityfirstfl.org/connect/contact-us "INFO24"), [Mobile](https://www.communityfirstfl.org/personal-banking/online-banking "Learn more about Mobile Banking") and [Online Banking](https://ebanking.communityfirstfl.org/cfcufonline/Uux.aspx?&_ga=2.251178950.1341183297.1604520138-1814686001.1604520138#/login "Click here to go to the Online Banking login page") will be available.

Login

Log into Online Banking

* Routing #263078934

    * Back
        * [Student Banking - Teen Accounts (13-17)](https://www.communityfirstfl.org/personal-banking/student-banking/student-banking-teen-accounts-(13-17))
    * Back
    * Back
    * Back
* Routing #263078934

* Legal Pages

Privacy Policy
==============

Effective 5.4.22

| **Facts** | What does Community First Credit Union of Florida  <br>do with your personal information?<br>-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- |
| --- | --- |
| **Why?** | Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do. |
| **What?** | The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:<br><br>* Social Security number and account balances<br>* credit card or other debt and credit scores<br>* mortgage rates and payments and retirement assets<br><br>When you are _no longer_ our member, we continue to share your information as described in this notice. |
| **How?** | All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members’ personal information; the reasons Community First CU of Florida chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing. |

| ### Reasons we can share your personal information | **Does Community First CU of Florida share?** | **Can you limit this sharing?** |
| --- | --- | --- |
| **For our everyday business purposes –**  <br>such as to process your transactions, maintain your  <br>account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or to report to credit bureaus | Yes | No  |
| **For our marketing purposes –**  <br>to offer our products and services to you | Yes | No  |
| **For joint marketing with other financial companies** | Yes | No  |
| **For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –**  <br>information about your transactions and experiences | Yes | No  |
| **For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –**  <br>information about your creditworthiness | No  | We don't share |
| **For our affiliates to market to you** | No  | We don't share |
| **For nonaffiliates to market to you** | No  | We don't share |
| **Questions?** Call toll-free [800-342-8416](tel: 800.342.8416 "Call 800-342-8416") |     |     |

| ### What we do |     |
| --- | --- |
| **How does Community First CU of Florida protect my personal information?** | To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings. |
| **How does Community First CU of Florida collect my personal information?** | We collect your personal information, for example, when you<br><br>* open an account or apply for a loan<br>* give us your employment information or apply for financing<br>* give us your contact information<br><br>We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies. |
| **Why can’t I limit all sharing?** | Federal law gives you the right to limit only<br><br>* sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness<br>* affiliates from using your information to market to you<br>* sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you<br><br>State law and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. |

| ### Definitions |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Affiliates** | Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.  <br>_\- Our affiliates include financial companies, such as Payment Systems for Credit Unions (PSCU)_ |
| **Nonaffiliates** | Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.  <br>_\- Community First Credit Union of Florida does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you_ |
| **Joint Marketing** | A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.  <br>_\- Our joint marketing partners include loan recapture programs and financial advisors_ |

Rev. 5.22

Corp. NMLS#: 379502

Your savings are federally insured to at least $250,000 and backed by the full faith and credit of the United States Government. The National Credit Union Administration is a U.S. Government Agency.

© Community First Credit Union of Florida 2024

All Rights Reserved
